(Sheldon:)That's what
tertiary friends are for.
(Raj(inside):)Who is it?
(Leonard:)It's Leonard.
(Raj:)You can't come in.
(Leonard:)I just want to talk to her.
(Raj:)I forbid it.
(Priya:)Open the door,
Rajesh.
(Raj:)You heard me.
(Raj:)I forbidded it.
"Forbidded" it?
"Forbaded" it?
(Priya:)Get out of the way.
(Priya:)What are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
(Priya:)I have business in Los Angeles.
(Leonard:)Why didn't you call?
(Raj:)Clearly, she was
sending you a message
(Raj:)to take a hike, Mike.
(Howard:)I'm sorry.
I thought about calling,
(Priya:)but I just wasn't sure if
seeing you was such a good idea.
(Leonard:)I know. Last time
I came on too strong.
(Leonard:)Can we talk in private?
(Raj:)No!
Sure.
(Raj:)It's completely inappropriate
for a single woman
(Raj:)to entertain a man in private.
(Raj:)If you insist on talking,
you must do it on the couch!
(Raj:)All right, you may talk in
the bedroom,
(Raj:)but I want this door
to remain open!